

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and are bound to ensue; and equal blame belongs to those who fail in of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

### **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult es or pursues or desires to obtain pain of itself, because it is pain, but because and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

# **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to res eos, qui ratione voluptatem sequi nesciunt, neque porro quisquam est, qui goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**





### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer ing able to do what we like best, every pleasure is to be welco' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2004

# **HONORS & AWARDS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 

2013 - 2014

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US ESIGN OR (DIS)CONTENT Among design professio

### **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

**01234567890** mbinhnv@topcv.com

# **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop Excel **English** Power Point • **Japanese** 

# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt ut word choice. So don't be afraid to use lorem ipsu and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from **US** universities